
const STORE = [
  {
    question: `What year was the HMS Bounty built?`,
    choices: [
      `1779`,
      `1784`,
      `1789`,
      `1780`
    ],
    answer: `1784`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the captain's name?`,
    choices: [
      `John Adams`,
      `James Cook`,
      `William Bligh`,
      `Philip Taylor`
    ],
    answer: `William Bligh`
  },
  {
    question: `What resource was the crew of the Bounty tasked with bringing back to England?`,
    choices: [
      `Pineapple`,
      `Breadfruit`,
      `Spices`,
      `Guava`
    ],
    answer: `Breadfruit`
  },
  {
    question: `On what day did the Bounty set sail for Tahiti?`,
    choices: [
      `December 25, 1789`,
      `December 5, 1784`,
      `December 18, 1789`,
      `December 23, 1787`
    ],
    answer: `December 23, 1787`
  },
  {
    question: `How many months did it take the crew to reach Tahiti?`,
    choices: [
      `8`,
      `10`,
      `12`,
      `18`
    ],
    answer: `10`
  },
  {
    question: `Why did the Bounty never make it back to England?`,
    choices: [
      `There was a mutiny`,
      `The ship sank`,
      `The crew decided to stay in the society islands`,
      `They were abducted by aliens`
    ],
    answer: `There was a mutiny`
  },
  {
    question: `After an unsuccessful attempt at landing on a nearby island due to hostile natives, where did Captain Bligh and his loyalists sail to next?`,
    choices: [
      `Auckland`,
      `Sydney`,
      `Bali`,
      `Coupang`
    ],
    answer: `Coupang`
  },
  {
    question: `Where did the mutineers first try to settle?`,
    choices: [
      `Tupua'i`,
      `Moorea`,
      `Bora Bora`,
      `Nuku Hiva`
    ],
    answer: `Tupua'i`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the sailing vessel sent by the Royal Navy to capture the mutineers?`,
    choices: [
      `HMS Endeavour`,
      `HMS Justice`,
      `HMS Resolution`,
      `HMS Pandora`
    ],
    answer: `HMS Pandora`
  },
  {
    question: `Where did the mutineers who avoided capture eventually settle?`,
    choices: [
      `Hawaii`,
      `Mangareva`,
      `Pitcairn`,
      `Faka Rava`
    ],
    answer: `Pitcairn`
  }
];